Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(Episode 6)
Don't come near me.
It wasn't me.
I didn't do anything.
Who's there?
Who?
Who is it?
I didn't do anything.
It really wasn't me.
A ghost!
The game has already begun.
You all need to be smart.
If you're too stupid,
you might die.
She's so timid.
Your Highness!
Lu Zhao...
Lu Zhao has become an evil spirit!
She has come back to take our lives!
Your Highness must believe me!
I'm not lying to you!
She's going to kill all of us!
We'll all die!
Xue Er!
Your Highness.
Please save me, Your Highness!
Let's leave.
Let's forget about the Lu family's assets.
Let's leave now!
- Let's leave now! - Liu Ying Xue!
Calm down.
Whether she truly lost her memory...
or is faking it,
this is our best chance to seize the Lu family's assets.
The Lu family of Jiangnan...
is richer than the entire nation.
That's billions of silver taels!
Once our great plan succeeds,
the hardships you are enduring now...
will not be in vain.
I promise you.
What do you say?
But I'm really not just throwing a tantrum this time.
Your Highness must believe me.
After Lu Zhao woke up this time,
she was like a different person.
She knows martial arts now.
She even killed Du Juan.
She used to be a weak woman.
How could she be so good at killing people now?
There must be something fishy.
Your Highness,
you must be careful of her.
She knows martial arts?
If that's the case,
let's go to the Liu manor tomorrow.
I'll find an assassin...
to test her.
(Xuntian Sect)
Stop.
I don't want to fight anymore.
Chief.
Has there been progress...
with Master?
That Princess of Chu, Lu Zhao,
fell to her death just as I was performing the ritual.
Then, she mysteriously came back to life.
Before my sister died,
she gave her a jade pendant.
She promised to help her.
They had known each other long before.
Most importantly,
- on her body... - Her body?
Where on her body?
You looked at her body?
Anyway, I'm sure...
that Lu Zhao is my sister.
When are we going to bring Master back then?
She doesn't remember anything now.
Tell her then.
With her intelligence,
would she be afraid of ghosts and spirits?
Besides, to save her,
you sacrificed...
Ling Su.
I'm not as selfless as you think.
Everything I've done...
was just for my own sake.
Isn't it even better that she doesn't remember anything?
From now on,
we're not siblings anymore.
You're crazy.
I'm not crazy.
From now on,
our identities won't get between us.
She won't have any reason...
to push me away anymore.
Why can't two people who love each other be together?
I won't give in.
Let me try one last time.
One last time.
(Liu Manor)
Lu Zhao.
This...
This is...?
Lu Zhao.
Do you really not remember?
Please don't blame me.
After the accident,
other than my husband,
I don't remember...
anyone else.
It's fine.
This time,
I brought you home...
so you can try some familiar dishes.
Then, perhaps...
you'll remember something.
This is your father.
This is your aunt.
And this is your cousin,
Liu Ying Xue.
So you're my father...
and my aunt.
Yes.
The two of you...
were sitting so close.
I thought...
you were a married couple.
It's just that...
my surname is Lu,
but Father's surname is Liu.
Why is that?
Lu Zhao.
It's like this.
Your mother's surname is Lu.
Your father...
married into the Lu family.
That makes sense.
So Father married into the Lu family.
All right.
Your Highness.
Let's serve the dishes first.
The dishes will get cold in this cold weather.
Right.
Quick.
Have a seat.
Hurry, serve the dishes.
- Hurry. - Be careful.
These are...
Eels are plump in the winter.
It's the best season to eat them.
Lu Zhao, when you were at home,
you loved the eel feasts...
made by our chef.
You're right, Father.
This is Stir-Fried Eel.
This is Stir-fried Eel with Scallions.
This is Oil-drizzled Shredded Eel.
And this is eel soup.
They're all Jiangnan-style dishes.
I'm sure...
Lu Zhao will love them.
That's right, Lu Zhao.
Eels are rare.
You must eat more.
- Okay. - Here.
Lu Zhao's birth mother committed suicide...
by jumping into the river.
When her body was fished out,
it was dismembered.
It was covered in eels.
Since then,
whenever Lu Zhao saw eels,
she would feel nauseous and vomit.
It was a physiological reaction.
You can't fake that.
That makes things easier then.
What's the matter?
Lu Zhao.
Don't you usually...
love eating eels the most?
I don't remember.
Thank you, Your Highness,
for being so thoughtful.
Here.
Try it while it's hot.
Okay.
It's indeed delicious and rich.
How dare you, Liu family!
You're ruthless for riches!
I'll slaughter you all today!
- Be careful, my dear! - Your Highness!
Guards!
Catch this criminal!
Lu Zhao!
Why did you take the blade for me?
As long as...
you're safe and sound...
I...
don't want anything else.
Lu Zhao!
Summon the physician!
Summon the physician! Hurry!
Your Highness!
Xue Er.
Lu Zhao!
Lu Zhao.
There's something...
you must listen to carefully.
This is not the time.
Staying alive is more important.
Stay still.
Let me see your injury.
My dear.
I heard from the servants...
that my grandfather...
is the richest man in Jiangnan,
And I...
am the only heir of the Lu family.
If anything happens,
I don't want to see...
all the Lu family's assets...
go to other branches of the clan.
My dear,
what do you...
mean by that?
Your Highness,
I've written a letter...
addressed to my clan elders in Jiangnan.
All the Lu family's assets shall be transferred...
to your manor.
You'll be in charge of it.
It's just that...
the elders of Jiangnan...
will only believe it...
if I confirm it myself.
When the time comes,
you can...
- Lu Zhao. - ...take this letter...
Lu Zhao!
Your Highness, this is our physician.
Check her pulse. Hurry!
There are too many people here.
The turbid air is disturbing.
Please leave.
I'll do my best to treat Her Highness.
Do your best to treat her.
When she recovers,
I'll promote you to the head steward of my manor.
If anything happens to her,
I'll bury you with her!
Yes, Your Highness.
I'm a spy from the Xuntian Sect.
Greetings, Ms. Lu.
Are you injured?
It's just a pack of chicken blood.
Do you not trust...
your master's aim?
Do you trust me that much?
Situ Xian is already suspicious about your amnesia.
He hired an assassin...
to test you at the Liu family dinner.
Remember not to expose yourself.
If he wants to test me,
why don't I just play along with him...
so that he won't suspect me again?
I need an insider.
The female physician of the Liu manor...
has been my spy for years.
She can be of use to you.
That's perfect.
Of course.
Someone who's part of the Xuntian Sect...
wouldn't be some petty criminal.
Don't worry.
I will protect you no matter what.
That's enough, Xue Er.
What's the use of crying?
Mother.
There's really something wrong with her.
You have to believe me.
She's just pretending to have lost her memory.
Go back first.
Tomorrow,
I'll find a way to expose that wench.
Your Highness.
How is the Princess's injury?
I just sent someone to ask.
She didn't injure any vital organs.
It's just a superficial wound.
She should recover by tomorrow morning.
She took the blade for me.
I don't think...
she's faking it.
I heard from the female physician...
that if the assassin's sword was one inch off,
it would have pierced her heart.
Hurry up and take this letter to Jiangnan.
Bring the chief of the Lu clan...
to Ying.
During this time,
Lu Zhao...
must not suffer any mishaps.
Yes.
Does she really not remember anything?
Didn't you say you'd take me to His Highness?
Why did you bring me here?
His Highness is here.
You can go by yourself.
Aunt.
What are you doing?
Lu Zhao.
Come and take a look at who this is.
Pull her up.
Nanny?
This old woman is a thief.
She stole from the manor.
Of course, she has to suffer.
Aunt.
This is the Prince of Chu's manor.
You shouldn't kill a servant like this.
I'm afraid it's inappropriate, Aunt.
So Your Highness remembers this old woman?
You want to save her life?
If Your Highness recognizes her,
then for Your Highness's sake,
I'll spare her life.
But...
if Your Highness doesn't recognize her either,
then I'll drown her immediately...
as a warning to the others.
You can fool His Highness,
but you can't fool me.
If you don't admit to faking your memory loss...
and setting up this trap,
I'll kill this vile servant!
How dare you try to test me?